Doesn't look good
Looks good
No need to be nervous
I'm not nervous
Then what is it
I just find it interesting
The whole city used to laugh at me
Now it's the Fu family branch's turn
No one has the right to laugh at you
Don't speak too soon
The more entitled some people feel
The harder the slap in the face will be later
Wenyao watch your words tonight
I know Dad
Randomly picking someone at the wedding
And getting the Fu family heir
Everyone praises his good taste
But I think he's just lucky
I heard he was originally engaged to the Gu family
And only switched partners on the wedding day
Such a coincidence
Ah
Chen Zhou Mingyao come here
Let me introduce you to everyone